



NGO TRONG NGHIA SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

<u>4</u> 24-10-1991

01667 319 803

27 Nguyen Van Sieu, Da Nang

nghia.ngo.2410@gmail.com
nghia-ngo.github.io



SUMMARY

Experiencing over 5 years in software development, especially, out-sourcing for Japanese clients including 2 years of programming Window application, using .NET and over 3 years of web developing using .NET MVC and Java Spring.

- Be responsible and careful in tasks implement.
- Be ability to learn guickly and master about technologies and business.
- Be ability to judge, refer, self-study, learn and discuss to come up with solutions.



EXPERIENCE

SENIOR DEVELOPER, COWELL ASIA - DA NANG BRANCH

3/2015 until now

■ Golf booking system – GDO customer

System including websites which allows Japanese users to find information, booking golf and allows admins to manage golf and booking as well.

₹ Accomplishments

- Using VB.NET with ASP.NET MVC2 framework, Microsoft SQL, JS, HTML/CSS to develop new functions or maintain user websites.
- Using VB.NET with ASP.NET Web Forms framework, Microsoft SQL, JS to develop new functions or maintain admin system, including managing master information such as golf, plan, price, coupon... and managing booking.
- Creating matrix test and taking evidences.

Golf booking system has been developed from GDO system with improvements and applying new technologies.

₹ Accomplishments

- Using ASP.NET MVC3, HTML5/CSS3, JQuery to develope features.
- Using WOVN to show multi languages, InterFAX to send international fax, social login.
- Using fintech OMISE throught API to pay booking, including charging, capturing, refunding.
- Deploying system on dev/staging/product environments, using AWS with EC2 Windows Server 2012 IIS, DB is MySQL RDS, Simple Storage Service S3 which saves files.

■ Workflow system – MITANI customer

Workflow system, which is developed completely new to manage request including creating, approving, finding and showing request.



- Using JAVA Spring boot combined with Hibernate, JPA, Security Oauth 2, PostgreSQL, Mail to establish API back-end system.
- Using Angular 4 combined with framework HTML5 IgniteUI, Bootstrap, HTML5/CSS3 to establish front-end system.
- Deploy system using AWS with server is Amazon linux, DB is PostgreSQL RDS, Simple Storage S3 to save pictures, logos, attached files when creating request.

Q Achievement

- Best GDO team award 2015.
- Best quality member award 2016.
- MVP award 2017.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, FUJINET CO.,LTD - HCM

3/2013 - 2/2015

Factory-ONE system – EX corporation customer

Windows application system, which is using by factories to manage materials, status and acting.

₹ Accomplishments

- Using VB.NET, Oracle to develop new or edit application screen depend on detail of
- Implement test according to checklist and take evidences.

ERP system Super Cocktail – UCHIDA YOKO customer

ERP system will be customized base on request of every client.

₹ Accomplishments

- Taking responsibilities of editing and adding new functions related to report module, inventory, debt managing and lack of sale.
- Using VB.NET, WinForm with customize control to establish interface.
- Using SQL, PL/SQL with DB Oracle to guery and save data.
- Using Crystal Report to propose the report.

ERP system Super Cocktail Vietnamize

₹ Accomplishments

- Taking responsibilities of Vietnamese ERP system for module to propose report, inventory managing, using C#, DevExpress.



EDUCATION

A LANGUAGES

BARCHELOR IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY : - Japanese: N4

HCM City University of Sciences, 2009-2013 **Rank: Distinction**

- English: reading and writing English fluently



- Main programing languages: .NET (Code.Score: 76 A), Java (Code.Score: 47 B).
- Framework: ASP.NET MVC, Spring boot with Hibernate.
- Front-end: Angular 4, JS, HTML5/CSS3, Bootstrap.
- Other: SVN, GIT, AWS.